{
    "subject": "resource/Josh_Homme",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedMusicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Mark_Lanegan",
    "human_readable": "Josh Homme is associated with Mark Lanegan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9688127040863037,
            "question": "What is the nature of the association between Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9232923984527588,
            "question": "In what musical genres are Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan involved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8946031928062439,
            "question": "How long have Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan been associated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8695860505104065,
            "question": "Who is Josh Homme associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8424047827720642,
            "question": "Is there a specific project or album where Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan collaborated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8326012492179871,
            "question": "Are there any notable differences in the musical approaches of Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.826471745967865,
            "question": "What are some of the similarities between Josh Homme's and Mark Lanegan's musical styles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8193334341049194,
            "question": "Have Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan collaborated on any projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8027752637863159,
            "question": "Are there any other musicians besides Mark Lanegan that Josh Homme has worked with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5423551201820374,
            "question": "What is Mark Lanegan known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Josh Homme is associated with Mark Lanegan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7869_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other musicians besides Mark Lanegan that Josh Homme has worked with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7869_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Have Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan collaborated on any projects?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7869_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the similarities between Josh Homme's and Mark Lanegan's musical styles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7869_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7869_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7869/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt, Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan have an extensive history together, having met in the 1990s and worked together in the band Screaming Trees for a summer tour. They also became close friends before tensions arose."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Josh Homme and Mark Lanegan have a long-standing musical relationship, having worked together in various projects such as Kyuss, Screaming Trees, Queens of the Stone Age, and co-writing songs for Travel Channel series. This association is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}